Micael Moraes

Full-Stack Web Developer

Micael Barreto de Moraes

R. Mal. Floriano Peixoto Videira - SC, 89560-110, Brazil

Phone: +55 (11) 9 9555-4573

E-mail: micaelmoraes.dev@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/MicaelBarreto

Professional Summary

Full-stack web and mobile developer with 3+ years experience developing, designing, testing, system management and software engineering. Developed and designed a lot of advanced applications always trying to improve my coding skills in several languages like PHP, Javascript, C, HTML, CSS and some frameworks/libraries like Node, React, Laravel, Sass, Bootstrap and much more. Skilled with Containerization using Docker and web server management

Experience

Sysfar / Freelancer

October 2019 - PRESENT, REMOTE

- Worked as Full-Stack Web Developer and Web Server Manager.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Cloud and Web Technologies.

Prefeitura Municipal de Videira (Videira City Hall) / Internship

October 2018 - March 2020, VIDEIRA

- Worked as Full-Stack Web and Mobile Developer.
- Implemented and updated applications under the direction of Senior Software Developers.
- Also performed as Software Engineer, Team Manager and DevOps.
- Performed automated testing tasks and developed complex features routinely.

Education

Computer Science at Instituto Federal Catarinense / Bachelor

March 2017 - PRESENT, LOCATION

Algorithms, Web Design, Software Engineering, Software Security, UI/UX, Mathematics for Computer Science, Software and Hardware Architecture, etc.

Skills

- PHP 5.6+ and Frameworks/Libraries (Laravel, Lumen, Slim, Tests,)
- Javascript and Frameworks/Libraries (Pure, Node, React, JQuery)
- HTML5
- CSS and Frameworks (Bootstrap)
- Sass
- Git
- Linux and Windows
- Docker
- Software Engineering
- UX
- Team Management
- Documentation (Swagger, Docz)

Languages

- Portuguese Native Speaker
- English Highly Proficient
- Spanish Working Knowledge